Now we know and understand what Chrome files are.
Now let's see how actually create one and use it in your daily workflow.
You see how easy it is to set up a new prompt file, test it and run it whenever you need.
So let's start with creating prompt files.
Creating prompt files is really simple.
But before we create it, we look at some examples for the prompt files,
so there is some documentation.
So there are two examples.
The first one to generate the form component.
And next one to perform security review of press API.
We have in our project.
The first one is to learn when previous lesson has some header information.
We specify the mode.
We'd like to use the edge and edit or ask mode.
We can specify a model.
We can also specify tools like it has access to GitHub repository to source the code base.
If you'd like, you can also skip it.
And I will decide what tools you need.
And you can add some description like it will be shown in user interface.
Then you describe the instructions that you go with to generate new React form component based on a place from GitHub repository.
And then you ask for the form name and fields if not provided.
So here I will ask us for the form name and some fields.
And there are some rules it should follow when creating it.
And another one is for the API.
You see it's a bit shortened.
We have ask mode.
We have model.
And we have description.
So we doesn't specify those right here.
And you see, the goal of this one is to review an API.
We already haven't provided some to do list of security issues.
And we have a list of instructions.
And we also ask the eye in what format to return the result.
So let me show you how to create this prompt.
So, okay.
I just got the paste it.
You can also hear right here that the prompts should have the same name and convention as instructions, but just the prompts.
And we also can put them into folder prompts.
And now you can create a new prompt.
So this one will be about, let's say, React form.
So, React form, sorry, React form dot prompt dot MD.
Let me quickly check here dot prompt.
It should be dot prompt.
Okay.
And now we can paste the prompt right here.
And let's do it for the one more prompt for the.
For an API, let's check API security.
Or maybe I review just API review prompt dot MD.
And you'll paste it here.
When you see a prompt, you start here.
And it could like, for example, use this prompts right here.
So you can click slash.
And start writing the prompt name.
For example, redirect form.
Yeah, we can add the message context.
Okay.
And now we can ask, for example, so we'll do ask.
To ask the cream, a form component for, again, add, again, form.
And let's see what the I will do.
You see, it user references the customer instructions.
Of course, you have to create the gain following the provided requirements.
First, blah, blah, blah.
Let me create a login form.
It's proper TypeScript.
Let's check what we'd like to use.
We'd like to use the code form for inside.
We also should use TypeScript.
Right here.
As you see, it used already TypeScript.
We have some validation file where we have.
Yep.
If we open a form, right here, we use the Act hook forms.
And it's really following instructions.
And we can also, it asks us to install all the libraries.
Okay.
We can allow it to install.
As you see, this prompts can save you a lot of time.
If you have some repetitive request, like you create in components with the same style.
Yeah, you can have a prompt.
To create this component and just provide a name, you can use variables as well.
This is so, in presentation, previous lesson.
And this really helps you to make it faster without repeating in actions.
So now you know how to use the prompts and how to use instructions.
And you have full pack for development with NEI, the faster development.
Okay.
It's really simple workflows that save time for you.
Just keep your prompts organized, basically our names, you or your members can read the name and understand what is it.
Also, add some description right here.
And also, then compile it.
We'll keep following your instructions as you expect it.
Okay.
I hope Slaton was useful for you and see you in the next lesson.